electjon.com 2019-02-07

# Take Action | Privacy Policy

Jon Ossoff for Congress cares about your privacy rights, and about providing you with the information you need in order to protect them. Accordingly, we’ve created this policy to explain our privacy practices. This applies to **[electjon.com](http://electjon.com/)** only.

We may revise and update this policy if our practices change, if we add new features to the site, or if we change existing ones that affect these practices. We may also modify this policy if we find better ways to inform you of products or services that we think will be of interest. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information.

 **Information Collected About You**

We collect a variety of personal information about those who register on our site, make contributions through our site or use other functions or features on the site. Personal information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, credit card information, bank account information, e-mail address, or information about activities that are directly linked to that person.

We collect information you give us when you register on our site, contact us or make an online contribution. For example, when making a contribution, in addition to providing us your name, address, occupation and name of employer, you will need to provide us a billing address and credit card or bank account information, and answer a series of brief questions to make sure we may legally accept your contribution.

You may make changes to the information you have provided by visiting any form throughout the **[electjon.com](http://electjon.com/)** site. You may also contact us at **[info@electjon.com](mailto:info@electjon.com)** with any questions or changes to your account.

Automatically Collected Information: We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us online. For example, when you visit our site, our systems automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser you use. Information may be automatically collected through the use of “cookies” (more information below). We also collect “clickstream” data about your use of the site.

 **Network And Information Security**

We employ a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personal information. For example, we use commercially reasonable tools and techniques to protect against unauthorized access to our systems. Also, we restrict access to personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide services to you. In addition, we work to protect the security of your personal information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and allows you to view your information in a secure manner. You should be aware that we have no control over the security of other sites on the Internet you might visit, interact with, or from which you buy products or services. Further, we store the personal information we collect from you behind a secure firewall and place the transaction site on a secure server.

 **Disclosure Of Personal Information**

Information about our donors and website visitors is one of our most important assets and therefore we keep it confidential. Personal information is made available to others for the following, limited purposes:

To Comply with Campaign Finance Laws. We are often required to disclose information regarding our contributions to comply with campaign finance laws. For example, federal law requires us to use our best efforts to collect and report the name, mailing address, occupation and name of employer of individuals whose contributions aggregate in excess of $200 in a calendar year.

To Carry Out Your Requests. We also may be required to disclose personal information in order to carry out your requests when you use the site. For example, we will share personal information with third parties as necessary to complete a donation transaction or to deliver an e-mail to someone you have identified or when we disclose your return address as part of the service.

To Protect You and Ourselves. We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena), to protect our rights or property, or to protect our donors and supporters from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful conduct, or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.

To Support Democratic Candidates and Organizations. We may disclose selected personal information (other than credit card or bank information) to other campaigns and organizations that we believe are like-minded or that we believe you may wish to hear from.

 **Cookies**

We may automatically collect information using “cookies” or cookie-like files called Local Shared Objects (Flash cookies). Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a Web site. Local Shared Objects are larger data files stored on your hard drive. Among other things, cookies and Local Shared Objects help us improve our site and your experience, count visits to our site and to tailor your experience on our site according to which areas you have visited on our site and the preferences you have specified, and to save you the effort of having to log in or provide information each time you visit our Web site. These cookies and Local Shared Objects may be linked to your personal information. Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our site. Browser settings will not affect Local Shared Objects.

 **Web Beacons**

We may collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our sites or in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. Third Party Advertisements

We may also use third parties to show you ads for other organizations on our site. We may also use third parties to show our ads on other organizations’ Web sites based on your prior visits to our site. To show these ads, these third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to our site and other Web sites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our site (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number). They do this using cookies, clear gifs or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our site and the other Web sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads or on third party Web sites, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these third parties, **[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)**.

 **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

We do not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13. To respect the privacy of children and to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any Personal Information on this Site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

 **Links To Other Sites**

Please be aware that we may provide links to third-party Web sites, including those sites maintained by Democratic candidates, other Democratic committees and news media outlets, as a service to our visitors. We are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites. Please note that these sites’ privacy policies may differ from ours. We encourage you to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information.

 **Updating This Policy**

We may revise or update this policy if our practices change, as we change existing or add new features or as we develop better ways to inform you of features we think will be of interest. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information. If we decide to change this policy, we will post a new policy on our sites and change the date at the top of the policy.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns, please contact us by e-mail at **[info@electjon.com](mailto:info@electjon.com)**.
